indi.com 2019-05-12

# 

This Policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you online. For some services, we either collect and transfer personal information to a service provider or merchant that you have selected, or you may visit other merchants or service providers through links on our site who may collect and use your personal information. In those cases the third-party service provider or merchant's privacy policy will govern how your information is handled. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others. _Except as limited below, we reserve the right to use or disclose your personally identifiable information for business reasons in whatever manner desired._ _All information collected from and provided by you will be shared with Indi's affiliated companies, and all successors and assigns thereto._ This Privacy Policy will explain the following regarding use of our site:

 **1\. What information does Indi collect from you?**

**2\. Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?**

**3\. Who is collecting your information?**

**4\. With whom do we share your information?**

**5\. How can you update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information?**

**6\. What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information**

**7\. What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**

**8\. A special note about children's privacy**

**9\. Indi and third-party use of "cookies" and "action tags."**

**10\. You should carefully review privacy policies of any third party sites accessible from Indi**

**11\. Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)**

**12\. Contact Us**

**13\. Privacy Policy changes**

* **What information does Indi collect from you?** In order to better provide you with the services offered on the Indi site, Indi collects two types of information about its visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our site. **Personally Identifiable Information** This refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. Personal information is requested in many ways, for example, when you register and set up an account, post on the Indi site, register for a product or service, enter challenges or sweepstakes, apply for a credit card, fill out surveys, and send us feedback. For example, this information might include your name, billing address, shipping address, Face Book ID, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other payment information, and product details. With this information, Indi can better provide you with personalized services. For some third party services, we may collect your personal information on behalf of these service providers and share it with them. **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** This refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on, and how you use, our site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. For example, this information may include gender, geographic location, genres, categories and channels you interact with, the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, cookies, device information, your Internet Protocol ("IP") address and NPII third party information passed to us from your third party registration on Indi (e.g., from Face Book login). A URL is the global address of documents and other resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for a computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks like the Web use the TCP/IP protocol to route information based on the IP address of the destination. In other words, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, allowing web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers require IP addresses in order for users to communicate on the Internet, browse and shop. On an aggregated basis, we collect anonymous data related to the pages, posts, communications, products, downloads and other content that is sampled, clicked on, streamed, searched for, transferred from and downloaded. When content on Indi is shared into social media, that content may be tagged and tracked in social media for primary purposes of Buzz determination, and the social media site may pass back certain information such as likes, shares, comments and other interactions that such content receives within the social media network. Except as otherwise limited in this Policy, we may disclose, share, sell, trade, or rent Non-Personally Identifiable Information to others without your consent. 

* **Where do we collect information from you and how do we use it?** Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide Indi's visitors with a superior customized online experience. We use the customer contact information in many ways, including without limitation to communicate with customers, to inform them of their challenge status, to send promotional information, and to enhance the operation of our site and administer our systems. Demographic data also may be collected at our site from third party log-in services, advertising servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents who provide us with the zip code and area code associated with a visitor's server, along with pages viewed on our site. We review the actions of the Indi visitors on to determine customers' preferences. Indi also does research on our visitors' demographics, postings, interests, and pages viewed based on the information provided to us during content uploading, challenges, posting comments and reviews, a promotion, from our server log files, from our web site analysis agents, or from challenges, drawings, postings or surveys. We will use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site use, to improve our product and services offerings, and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We receive reports from third party ad servers, content servers, or web site analysis agents that tells us how many ads were presented and clicked upon or what content was served or viewed. We may also share your personally identifiable information with third parties who provide services to us, our customers and web site visitors. Those third parties include authorized contractors, temporary employees and consultants and other companies working with us (collectively, "agents"). Where we believe it to be appropriate (in our sole discretion), we will ask our agents not to disclose or use your personal information for purposes other than to provide services to you or Indi. We gather information in the following ways: **Use of the Site and Services Generally** We collect IP addresses, cookies and device and usage for the purposes of system administration, and gather broad demographic information, to enable ads to be served on our site and generally to report Non-Personally Identifiable Information to our advertisers and channel owners on Indi whose channel you have visited, and to monitor the level of activity on our site. We collect information from visitors to our site regarding the URLs they came from, domain types (e.g., .com or .org), their IP addresses cookies and device information, all geographic and demographic information, the date and time of their visit or various use, the number of visits and various uses, the number of visits per browsing session, the server type, the operating system and browser type used to come to the site, the country, state and telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages and page titles of our site that visitors viewed during their visit, whether the visitor's computer is enabled for Java or cookies, browser language, applications and plug-ins, and any search terms entered on our site. We also track customers' traffic patterns throughout their online session, including which pages, information and advertisements a customer views while using the site, content posting, communications and all other use of the Indi site. We also use your IP address to diagnose problems with our servers, software, to administer our site and to gather demographic information. We may share aggregated statistics about pages viewed on our site, sales and other shopping information with third parties. **Uploading Content** We track all aspects of the updload process to provide us with information to monitor and improve our uploading process. This information includes the file name, attributes and contents of the uploaded file. We also request additional information to pinpoint the date, time and your upload location and the location, place of business, etc. for where your video was filmed. **Action Tags/Web Beacons** We may use and allow others to use action tags or web beacons in the operation of our site; to find out what action tags and web beacons are and how they are used, click here. When content on Indi is shared into social media, that content may be tagged and tracked in social media for the primary purposes of Buzz determination, and the social media site may pass back certain information such as likes, shares, comments and other interactions that such content receives within the social media network. All of the foregoing Non-Personally Identifiable Information is shared with channel owners on Indi with respect to your visits on their channels, and Personally Identifiable Information may be transferred to a channel owner based on your agreement to share such information when uploading to a forum or challenge on the channel owners channel.

* **Who is collecting your information?** **Ad Servers and Content Servers** We may use third party ad servers or content servers to serve ads, product information, or other information both on and off our site. Those third parties may use "action tags" or web beacons throughout the site to count the number of visitors who click on a banner ad or other information and to track the number of customers who continue on to make a purchase. They may also place their own "cookie" on your computer to help those ads to run and analyze site usage. We do not provide them with any of your Personally Identifiable Information. For more information about the information they collect, please see the section "Use of Cookies and Action Tags" below. **Image Servers** We may use a third party image serving company to serve the graphics that visitors see on our site more quickly. They collect a visitor's IP address and the URLs of any graphics viewed and the date and time of the visit. However, they do not collect and we do not provide them with any Personally Identifiable Information. They may also use a "cookie." To learn more about their information practices, Click here. **Email Services** We may use a third party service provider to send promotional and other e-mails to customers. Images contained in the email may be served by the third party. They collect certain information about you such as your IP address, browser type, your operating system, the country and server your computer is logged onto, where the servers that your computer is logged onto is located, the time and date that a particular email was viewed, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular ad or email, products viewed and whether you continued on to make a purchase. They may use a "cookie" or "action tags." **Website Analysis Agent** We may contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and marketing. We use the services of marketing companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Action Tags and cookies provided by the marketing companies on this site. The type of information we collect includes things such as pages, information and advertisements viewed as well as what items are placed in a shopping basket or purchased, the order number, the amount of a purchase, the product number and the quantity purchased. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although the marketing companies log the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. For more information, please see the section "Use of Cookies and Action Tags" below. **Financing Services** We may use a third party bank to provide a credit card and financing to customers who desire it. The bank collects personally identifiable information to provide their financing services. **General Provision of Services and Site Operations** We contract with third-party service providers to operate many of our website functions. We may provide such third-party service providers with your other personal information as needed to operate many of our website functions. **Marketing Partners, Co-Branded Services, Framing/Windows on Third-Party Sites** We may run promotions for other service providers or merchants where you may visit the such service provider's or merchants' sites. In some of those promotions, a window or frame containing the merchant's site may appear. Any time you are in a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with that service provider's or merchant's policies. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you supply to those service providers and merchants. Any information that you share with them will be used and disclosed in accordance with that service provider's or merchant's privacy policy. However, once you click on a return link to our site, you can expect that further information that you disclose to us will be treated in accordance with this Policy. **Links and Banner Ads to Third-Party Sites** Please be aware that our site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies or ad servers, which place advertising on our site may collect information about you through the use of cookies when you view or click on their advertising. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. 

* **With whom do we share your information?** **Other Indi Members and Site Visitors** Your profile information and all postings (which may include your pictures and your name and any other information you post or allow to be shared with other members and visitors) are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the Indi social networking community. **PLEASE SEE THE TERMS OF USE FOR MORE INFORMATION REGARDING WHEN AND WHAT INFORMATION AND CONTENT IS AUTOMATICALLY DISPLAYED TO VISITORS AND INDI MEMBERS.** In addition, email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Indi, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. To facilitate searching and finding friends and members with similar interests on the service, Indi allows users to search for other members using screen names, email addresses and first and last name. Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily postinformation, that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. **Invitations and Other Communications to Non-members** You can invite friends to join the service by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. Indi stores the email addresses that you provide so that the respondents may be added to the friend's list of the member sending the invitations, and also to send reminders of the initial invitation you send. Indi does not sell or rent these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations, and invitation reminders. **Channel Owners on Indi** All Non-Personally Identifiable Information associated with your visits and use on their channels is shared with channel owners on Indi, and Personally Identifiable Information may be transferred to a channel owner based on your agreement to share such information when uploading to a forum or challenge on the channel owners channel. **Payment Processing** We will disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third party payment processors to facilitate your purchases on the Indi site. **Other Parties Generally** We may provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' to third parties, including aggregated statistical information which does not include any Personally Identifiable Information. We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use, Challenge Rules or to protect the rights, property, and safety of Indi, our users, or others. If customers do not pay us for products/services ordered, we may submit their account information to a third party collection agency. We may also share your Personally Identifiable Information with third parties who provide services to us, to our customers and to our web site visitors. Those third parties include authorized contractors, temporary employees and consultants and other companies working with us such as Buy Services (collectively, "agents"). Where we believe it to be appropriate (in our sole discretion), we will ask our agents not to disclose or use your personal information for purposes other than to provide services to you or Indi. **Data Analysis Agents** The information collected by or for Indi may be provided to an outside company for the purpose of analysis. That analysis is to help us to improve our site and product selection, and to notify you of special offers that may be of interest to you. That data analysis agent may not share any Personally Identifiable Information with others, or use it for any other purpose than to help Indi. **Ad & Content Servers, Advertisers, Image Servers and Website Analysis Agents** These third parties use their cookies' identification numbers and internal web site tracking features to serve ads on our site and to collect aggregated information to create statistics about our customers and visitors, traffic patterns, and related site information. In the event that our ad servers collect any Personally Identifiable Information on our behalf, it will not be used by them or disclosed to any third parties. To find out more information about our current website analysis agents information practices, click [here](http://www.kissmetrics.com/user-privacy) and [here](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). **Compliance with Service of Process or Law Enforcement** Occasionally Indi may be asked by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation, without notice to you. Indi fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we believe to be unlawful. **Challenges, Sweepstakes and Drawings** Where you enter a sweepstakes, drawing or other promotion, we may provide entry information, including name, address, email address and age to the company providing the prize or sponsoring the promotion. They may use your Personally Identifiable Information to send you marketing or promotional materials or other communications. **Sale of the Company or Assets** Indi and its affiliated companies each reserve the right to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in the event that any such company is sold, in whole or in part, either as an entire corporate entity or through an asset sale that includes a customer information database. This right is reserved whether or not the customer database is sold independently of any continuing operations of such company. 

* **How can you update or correct your Personally Identifiable Information?** We believe you should have the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided to us. You may modify any of your personal information in your account online at any time, provided that any such modifications are fully accurate. We encourage you to promptly update your information if it changes. You may ask to have the information on your account deleted or removed; however, because we keep track of past use of the site, transactions, postings, submissions, challenges, conversions and redemptions, you cannot delete information associated with such actions. Also, as a security measure we "back up" the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. As a result, you should not expect that all of your Personally Identifiable Information will be completely removed from our backed-up databases.

* **What are your choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information?** Ad-servers and other Content Servers: You may also set your browser so that it will not accept "cookies" to prevent assignment from the ad server of a unique identifier; however, you may experience difficulty using the features and services on the Indi site, shopping on any merchant site, and performing other transactions if you do so.

* **What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?** Within Indi, your information is kept on password protected, limited access servers. Wherever possible and applicable, Indi servers reside behind a corporate firewall that maintains controls on access to the system from both our internal network and the Internet. 

* **A special note about children's privacy** Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors under 13 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 years of age and believe that they have disclosed personally identifiable information to us, please contact us at privacy@indi.com so that we may delete the child's information. 

* **Indi and third-party use of "cookies" and "action tags."** Indi Cookies: When you use our site we will store cookies on your computer in order to facilitate and customize your use of our site. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to Indi. Our cookies store randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your name and profile image location to welcome you back to our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. Ad Server and Content Server Cookies: We may use an outside ad serving company or content server to display banner advertisements and other information on our site or to serve promotional emails. As part of their service, they place a separate cookie on your computer. Except for the company that serves our promotional emails, Indi does not provide third-party ad servers with any of your Personally Identifiable Information. Indi and its third party ad servers do collect and use Non-Personally Identifiable Information about you, such as your IP address, browser type, the URLs from which you came, referring site's domain types (e.g., .com), operating system, the country, the server your computer is logged onto, where the servers that your computer is logged onto is located, the pages of our site and products that visitors viewed during their visit, where an ad was placed on a specific web site page, the time and date particular ads were served, the area code and zip code associated with your server and whether you responded to a particular ad, and a receipt identifier. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices of the company that sends our emails, please click [here](http://sendgrid.com/privacy.html). Our third-party ad servers will occasionally use outside agents, whose computers will serve ads on our site in the same manner and under the same conditions as above. In addition, other ad serving companies or advertisers may place banner ads on our site in the same manner as above, but we do not disclose to them any Personally Identifiable Information. Image Server Cookies: As part of the ad-serving process, a third party may serve graphics upon our site. In order to customize their service, they may also place a cookie upon your computer. While Indi does not control their use of that cookie, no Personally Identifiable or individual customers' product information is collected. Website Analysis Agent Cookies: We may use a third party to analyze what our visitors find to be most interesting on our site. To do that, they will place a cookie on your computer with a randomly assigned unique number in order to track the pages you view on our site, along with other Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Action Tags, Web Beacons and other Data Collection Methods: An action tag or a web-beacon (also known as a clear gif or a pixel tag) is a method used to track responses or actions by customers who view certain advertisements or other information on our site. Action tags are 1x1 pixel images embedded in a website page that are used to transparently collect information. Our ad server, content servers and website analysis agents may use action tags to count the number of times that visitors click on a particular banner ad or visit the pages of our site and to provide information about what products are viewed or purchased. Without collecting any personally identifiable information, they use that data to tell us (and other advertisers) which ads are the most effective on particular sites. Our ad server, content server and website analysis agents may use an action tag on our basket page, checkout page, and other pages, to keep anonymous track of the number of times that clicking on a banner ad or views other information on our siteresults in a purchase. They also collect the amount of the purchase, order confirmation number, stock keeping unit number, quantity and identity of product or service purchased. E-mail Distributor's Use of Action Tags: Our third-party e-mail distributor may also use action tags. They may, for example, keep track of when a promotional e-mail is opened and provide Indi with ongoing aggregated reports of how many customers have responded. We share with them web site usage information about visitors to our web site who have received a promotional e-mail or other targeted promotional campaign. They use the information for the purpose of targeting future campaigns and upgrading visitor information used in reporting statistics. For this purpose, we and our third-party e-mail distributor note some of the pages you visit on our web site through the use of action tags. For more information about our third-party e-mail distributor's use of action tags and other data collection methods, please click [here](http://sendgrid.com/privacy.html). 

* **You should carefully review privacy policies of any third party sites accessible from Indi** Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection, use and disclosure practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. Indi is not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies that place advertising on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising through the use of cookies. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect. On behalf of various sponsors, Indi provides sponsored links to third-party web sites. If you click on a sponsored link or banner ad, a "window" or "frame" containing a third-party's web site may appear in the foreground with the Indi web site in the background. Unless you are on Indi's web site, any time that you have moved to a window, you should assume that your personal information is being collected, used and disclosed in accordance with the windowed site's privacy policy (if any). If you are unsure as to whose privacy policy applies, please contact us by sending a letter to the address below. Please be aware that unaffiliated third parties may "frame" Indi's site in an effort to collect customer information from you. To ensure your privacy, make sure that you have read and agree with the privacy policy of the site framing Indi. Indi is not in any manner responsible in the event that you do disclose information to an unaffiliated framing site.

* **Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”)** If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European law with respect to your personal data, including the right to request access to, correct, amend delete, port to another service provider, or object to certain uses of your personal data. If you have any questions about whether this section applies to you, please contact us using the information set forth in the “Contact Us” section below. **_Data Subject Rights:_** Indi acts as a controller of your Personal Data that is provided, collected and/or processed pursuant to this Privacy Policy. Note that when you engage with another channel on Indi and agree to provide that channel owner with Personal Data, that channel owner then also becomes the controller of your Personal Data and their use is governed by their privacy policy. You have certain rights with respect to your Personal Data as set forth below. Please note that in some circumstances, we may not be able to fully comply with your requests, or we may ask you to provide us with additional information in connection with your request, which may be Personal Data, for example, if we need to verify your identity or the nature of your request. In such situations, however, we will still respond to let you know of our decision. To make any of the following requests, contact us using the contact details referred to in the “Contact Us” section of this policy. **_Access and Portability:_** You can request a copy of the Personal Data. You have the right to ask for a copy of your Personal Data in a machine-readable format and can also request that we transmit the data to another entity where technically feasible. **_Corrections:_** If you believe that any Personal Data we are holding about you is incorrect or incomplete, you can request that we correct or supplement such data. You can also correct some of this information directly by logging into your account. **_Erasure:_** You can request that we erase some or all of your Personal Data from our systems. Please note that the erasure of even some of your data may make your channel inoperable and require the deactivation of the channel. **_Withdrawal of Consent:_** If we are processing your Personal Data based on your consent (as indicated at the time of collection of such data), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note, however, that (a) that the removal of processing of your Personal Data may make your channel inoperable and require the deactivation of the channel and (b) in order to interact with any other channel on Indi you will be required to provide express consent on a case-by-case basis for the use or disclosure of certain of your Personal Data and your latter consent will re-activate the processing of your Personal Data. **_Right to File Complaint:_** You have the right to lodge a complaint about Indi's practices with respect to your Personal Data with the supervisory authority of your country or EU Member State. **_Transfer & Storage:_** Indi's services and platform is hosted and operated in the United States (“U.S.”) through Indi and its service providers. We may transfer your Personal Data to the U.S., to any Indi affiliate worldwide, or to third parties acting on our behalf for the purposes of processing or storage. **_By using any of our platform or services or providing any Personal Data for any of the purposes stated above, you consent to the transfer and storage of your Personal Data, whether provided by you or obtained through a third party, to the U.S. as set forth herein, including the hosting of such Personal Data on U.S. servers._**

* **Contact Us** If you have any requests as set forth above or questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact Indi by sending an email to: privacy@indi.com. As a California resident you can ask in writing for a notice identifying the categories of personally identifying information we share to third parties for marketing purposes and providing contact information for such third party.

* **Privacy Policy changes** This Privacy Policy was last changed on May 24,2018. If Indi makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.
